http://www.uwstout.edu/university-wisconsin-stout-privacy-statement

University of Wisconsin-Stout Privacy Statement | University of Wisconsin - Stout
University of Wisconsin-Stout Privacy Statement
The University of Wisconsin-Stout collects a variety of information through this website.
Minnesota Reciprocity, MSEP, and Return to Wisconsin
Tax Reporting (Form 1098-T)
Tech Tips Newsletter - Cloud-based Collaboration Tools
Tech Tips Newsletter - Collaboration and Teamwork Assessment
Tech Tips Newsletter - Collaborative and Team-based Learning
Tech Tips Newsletter - Creating Audio Feedback
Tech Tips Newsletter - Creating Outstanding Rubrics
Tech Tips Newsletter - Critical Evaluation
Tech Tips Newsletter - Digital Badges for Teaching and Training
Tech Tips Newsletter - Password and Security Tips
Tech Tips Newsletter - Plagiarism-Proofing Assignments and Assessments
Tech Tips Newsletter - Plagiarism-Proofing Assignments and Paraphrasing
Tech Tips Newsletter - Using Social Media
Tech Tips Newsletter - Web Tools for Creating and Curating Videos
Community of Practice
Scholarship of Teaching and Learning (SoTL)
Colleges & Schools
College of Arts, Communication, Humanities and Social Sciences
Art and Art History Department
Communication Technologies Department
Cybersecurity Research & Outreach Center (CyROC)
Clinical Services Center
Emerging Center for Career and Technical Education Excellence
Evelyn Van Donk Steenbock Endowed Chair
Initiative for the Creation of the Center for the Study and Promotion of Health and Wellbeing
Kinesiology, Health, Food and Nutritional Sciences Department
Teaching, Learning and Leadership Department
College of Science, Technology, Engineering, Mathematics and Management
Accreditation
Council for Accreditation of Counseling & Related Educational Programs
Play for Stout
What is Esports?
Wellness Week
RockFest!
Plastics Technology Certificate
Preventive Controls For Human Food Training (PCQI)
Early Childhood Education Preconference on Trauma
Family and Consumer Sciences Education & WI DPI Child Care Conference
Stout Vocational Rehabilitation Institute
Are You at a Higher Risk for Serious Illness from COVID-19?
Collaborations and Partnerships
Directions to SVRI
Important Press Release for SSI Recipients and Economic Impact Payments
Eligibility and Order of Selection Unit
Plan for Achieving Self Support (PASS)
Pre-Driving Evaluation & Training
Soft Skills Training
Work Incentive Benefits Analysis
States and Territories must submit a new four-year WIOA State Plan for Federal Review and Approval.
UW-Stout 2020-2030 Strategic Plan
The University of Wisconsin-Stout collects a variety of information through this website. UW-Stout is the sole owner of all information collected through this site, and it does not sell, share, rent, or otherwise disclose this information except as described in this statement. Information may be collected at various points on the site and may change without notice. Use of this website is voluntary. By using this website, you agree to allow UW-Stout to collect and use any information you provide using the site, including personally identifiable information (“PII”) and non-personal information as described in this Privacy Statement.
Image and Photo Policy
Written permission is not required when capturing the images of any individuals present in public settings in or around UW-Stout, or when the resulting photographs or videos are used in news and editorial contexts. This applies to images to be used in printed publications, displays, videos, web, or other formats. Exceptions for which UW-Stout recommends completion of participant release waiver include when an individual’s image, voice and/or name is captured with permission in a private setting, will be included in advertising materials in a format that implies endorsement of UW-Stout, or if the subject is a minor.
Participant Release
Participant_Release_Fillable_PDF.pdf
Whenever possible, university photographers/videographers identify themselves, seek verbal permission, and inform subjects about the potential uses of the photo or video. In any instance when an individual asks to not be photographed or videotaped, university photographers and videographers will comply. All photographic prints and digital photo/video files taken by university photographers and videographers constitute UW-Stout property, solely and completely.
Any image, even if captured in a public setting, used in any way an individual is not comfortable with will be removed upon request without question.
If you have any questions or concerns about the capture or use of an image, please contact marcom@uwstout.edu.
Collection and Use of Non-personal Information
Such information cannot be used to identify an individual personally. It is used to monitor site usage, health, and effectiveness, and it is also used to make improvements to the functionality and organization of the site. Non-personal information that may be collected and used includes, but is not limited to:
The Internet Protocol (IP) address and name of the Internet domain used to access the Internet
The IP address of the website that referred the user to the UW-Stout web site
The date and time of access
The pages visited
The web browser and operating system used to access the web site
Search terms used on the site
Collection of Personal information
Users may choose to voluntarily provide information on the site that could be used to identify them personally. This information is strictly voluntary – no personal information is collected unless the user provides it. Personal information that may be collected includes, but is not limited to:
Contact information
Employment information and history
Education history
References
Gift information
University affiliation
Information provided through online forms for a variety of purposes
For information on student privacy rights and our compliance to the Federal Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA), please refer to information hosted by our Registrar's Office.
Use of Personal Information
UW-Stout may use your personal information like that described above for the following purposes (this list may change without notice):
Administer users’ participation in this web site
Communicate information that may be of interest to users
Fulfill requests for services or materials
Contact users
Confirm information provided by users
Process gifts
Conduct research or surveys
Respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process
Facilitate interactions with third parties
Sharing Personal Information
Personal information provided to UW-Stout through this web site may be available to employees of the University or to authorized third parties who provide services to the University or to the users of this web site (www.uwstout.edu). Select third parties may be provided with personal information from this web site to help the University fulfill its mission. UW-Stout will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third parties are obligated to protect personal information on its behalf.
Collection Methods
UW-Stout may use various technologies such as cookies (small text files installed or updated when a web site is visited), applets, scripts, server logs, custom URL parameters, tracking images, information and correspondence, or web analytics to collect information. Depending on your browser you may be able to disable certain collection methods. This may limit your ability to use some features of this website.
Third party vendors, including Google, may use cookies on our Site.
We use the Google AdWords remarketing service-including the DoubleClick cookie and remarketing pixels-to advertise on third party sites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven't completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an inquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits to the Site. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy statement and Google's policy.
Opting out: You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page or the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
We also use certain Google Analytics features-including remarketing and advertising reporting features that leverage cookies and tracking pixels-to monitor user behavior on our site and to better target our advertising efforts.
Opting out: You can install a browser add-on to opt out of Google Analytics tracking.
Links to Other Sites
UW-Stout may provide links to other, third-party web sites from this site. Any such sites are regulated by the privacy policies of the providers of those web sites and not by this privacy statement. UW-Stout is not responsible for the privacy practices, security, or content of any third-party sites.  Your use of non-Stout websites is subject to the terms and conditions or privacy statements of the providers of those websites.
How We Protect Your Information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over an SSL-secured communication channel.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this Site or your experiences with this Site, or GDPR-related questions and requests, please contact us at:
Learning and Information Technology
University of Wisconsin-Stout
121 10th Avenue E
Menomonie, WI, 54751
Or e-mail helpdesk.uwstout.edu
715-232-5000
Privacy Statement last updated on Friday, March 8, 2019 at 10:00 AM.
Contact Information
Learning and Information Technology
105 Sorenson Hall
715-232-5320
Accessible Stout
UW-Stout strives to provide accessible web design for all people on all devices. Through Accessible Stout, our web editors strive to improve web usability for everyone, following designated training tools and guidelines. Our web editors constantly evaluate our usability using Core Web Editor Skills to create content we all can use. Currently, we are working to make our site screen-reader friendly for all devices.
Please contact us if you have a disability-related access issue.
Please contact us if you have a disability-related access issue.
